My mommy always said
there were no monsters.
No real ones.
But there are.
She's perfect.
Careful.
Two centimeters.
Yeah. Ready with that amnio.
And...
there it is.
But be careful.
Jesus!
Clamp.
What about her? Can we keep her alive?
How's the host?
Doing well.
Sew her back up.
Excellent work. Everybody.
- How is our Number Eight today?
- Appears to be in good health.
- How good?
- Excellent.
As in completely off our projected charts.
Look at the scar tissue.
See the recession?
- This is from three days ago?
- Exactly.
Well. this is good.
This is very good.
You're gonna make us all very proud.
Don't! I'm all right!
- Hand.
- Close.
Glove.
Number Eight?
- Fruit.
- Good. Cherries.
- It's unprecedented.
- Totally.
She's operating at
a completely adult capacity.
- What about her memories?
- There are gaps.
Some degree of synaptic dissonance.
She's freaked.
It has difficulties. caused by a biochemical
imbalance. causing emotional autism...
Wait a second. It has memories!
Why does it have memories?
I'm guessing. but inherited memories.
passed down generationally by the aliens.
like its strength.
Plus a highly evolved form of instinct.
Of course.
An unexpected benefit of the genetic process!
I didn't even think of that!
Let's try this one.
Ripley?
Ripley. what is it?
Ripley? Ripley?
- You're not thinking termination?
- Oh. boy. am I!
General. this is not a problem.
Ellen Ripley died
trying to wipe this species out.
For all intents and purposes. she succeeded.
I don't want her taking up old hobbies.
- That won't happen.
- We won't tell her.
Oh. I see. And that's supposed to comfort me.
Identification. please.
Please try again.
Thank you. General Perez.
The bottom line is. she looks at me funny
one time. I'm putting her down.
OK. as far as I'm concerned
Number Eight is a meat by-product.
Her Majesty here is the real payoff.
- When does she start producing?
- Days.
Less. maybe.
- We need the cargo.
- I told you. it's on its way.
Fork.
- Fuck.
- It's a fork.
How did you...
How did we get you?
Yes.
Hard work. We used blood samples.
from Fiori 16. on ice.
Where you died.
We've remade you. We cloned you.
Fiori 16.
Does that ring a bell?
Are you remembering something?
Does it grow?
Yeah. Very rapidly.
- It's a queen.
- How did you know that?
She'll breed.
You'll die.
Everyone in the company will die.
In the company?
Weyland-Yutani.
Ripley Eight's former employers.
A terran growth conglomerate. They had
defense contracts under the military.
They went under decades ago. Gediman.
Way before your time.
Bought out by Wal-Mart.
Fortunes of war.
I think you will find that things have
changed a great deal since your time.
I doubt that.
We're not flying blind. This is United Systems
Military. not some greedy corporation.
Well. it won't make any difference.
You're still gonna die.
How do you feel about that?
I wish you understood
what we're trying to do.
The potential for this species goes beyond
urban pacification: new alloys. new vaccines.
Nothing like this
we've ever seen on any world.
You should be very proud.
I am.
And the animal itself.
wondrous.
The potential. unbelievable.
Once we've tamed him.
Roll over? Play dead?
Heel?
You can't teach it tricks.
Why not? We're teaching you.
Hey. son. I'll give you
my authorization code.
It's E-A-T-M-E.
Could you repeat that?
Little prick.
You know. no matter
how many times you see it.
the sight of a woman all strapped up
in a chair like thatjust...
What?
Just bring us in on a 3-0 descent.
And ride the parallel.
- Darling. it is done.
- Good girl.
You want anything?
Yeah. How about a cup of coffee?
Anything else while your mouth's warm?
A little milk.
Hey. don't cut thrust till about 600 meters.
We'll give 'em a little scare.
Vriess! Call!
Goddamn. we're gonna die!
- Hey. Call?
- Yeah?
What has two thumbs. one eye.
a pink tongue.
and screws like a god?
What?
Two thumbs. one eye. a pink tongue.
and screws like a god?
What?
Time to enjoy some of
the general's hospitality. Christie.
Great. Army food.
Yeah. it'll do till we get
the family wagon up to spec.
That is. if the natives are friendly.
- How's that?
- Good.
Are we expecting any trouble?
From Perez. I doubt it. But you never know -
we've been there before.
What is wrong with you?
Just a little target practice.
Vriess isn't complaining.
Goddammit!
- Johner. you son of a bitch!
- Come on. man. you didn't feel a thing.
You are an inbred motherfucker.
you know that?
I'll take the knife back now.
Whoa...
Call. forget it.
He's been sucking down
too much home-brew.
The knife.
Son of a bitch!
Don't push me.
You hang with us for a while.
you'll find out I am not the man
with whom to fuck.
It's about time we started associating
with a better class of people.
I am Father.
Welcome to the USM Auriga.
Step forward for contraband
and weapons search.
Please report any infectious diseases
to the medical officers.
Levels seven through twelve
are off-limits to civilians.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Go.
- Hands up. please.
- What?
Could you get your hands up. please?
No weapons allowed on board. sir.
My own recipe.
Way more dangerous.
Nice welcome. Perez. What the hell is this?
Are you afraid the six of us
are gonna hijack your damn ship?
Just the concern that
one of your asshole crew members
is gonna get drunk and put a bullet through
the hull. We happen to be in space.
No shit.
How you been?
Wanna check the chair?
Elgyn. these were very. very hard to come by.
So was our cargo.
You're not about to plead poverty on me.
are you. General?
No. I'm just saying.
very few people deal in cash nowadays.
Just the ones don't like to keep
business records. Yourself. for example.
- Drink. Elgyn?
- Constantly.
I'm gonna take a wild guess here. General.
but I'm thinking
whatever you got going on here.
it ain't exactly approved by Congress.
Who's the new filly
you got on board. Elgyn?
Call?
She makes an impression.
She is severely fuckable. ain't she?
Mighty handy with a monkey wrench. too.
I might add.
I think Vriess has got
a bit of a light in his eye for her.
Fine little ass like that make a man walk.
you know what I mean?
Mind you. I think she's just a tad curious
about this transaction of ours.
I can't say as I blame her.
It's awfully cloak-and-dagger stuff.
It's a military operation.
Really?
Correct me if I'm wrong.
but I was under the impression that
most army medical labs don't operate
outside of regulated space.
What do you want?
What can I do for you?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Two days' bed and board.
Vriess might want to snag a part or two.
I mean. if it's not imposing.
I don't see any problem.
- A couple of conditions. though.
- Ah. conditions.
Not you. nor any of your
formidable crew members.
will go anywhere near restricted areas.
Rule number two.
- No trouble. Good behavior.
- Good behavior.
- No fights.
- No fights?
Mi casa es su casa.
Please direct cargo to medlab centre. area G.
Follow the lit path.
Do not deviate.
Cargo status stable.
Life forms intact.
Stasis uninterrupted.
Medlab centre is off-limits to civilians.
Thank you.
- Oh. please.
- You know I can't lay off the tall ones.
How ya doin'?
How about a little one-on-one?
Whaddaya say?
You got some moves on you. girl.
If you don't wanna play basketball.
I know some other indoor sports.
Come on. now. give me the ball.
OK... I got a new game.
Tag.
Ripley!
Ripley.
You've had enough fun.
What the hell are you?
Something of a predator. isn't she?
Yes. she continues to make us all very proud.
There's just one minute and 30 seconds left
to order this collector's item.
Jesus Christ. Johner.
what did you put in this shit? Battery acid?
Just for colour.
So. we're a fast learner.
This is a really good show. man.
Woman. that shit is not easy to come by!
Why don't you take a walk outside?
Great!
I'm so sorry.
If bitches can't handle this shit.
they should stay away from this shit!
Identification. please.
Please try again.
Thank you. General Perez.
Well?
Are you gonna kill me. or what?
There's no point. is there?
They've taken it out of you.
Where is it? Is it on the ship?
You mean my "baby"?
I don't get it. If they took it out.
why are they keeping you alive?
Well. they're curious. I'm the latest thing.
Look. I can make it all stop.
The pain. this nightmare.
That's all I can offer you.
What makes you think
I would let you do that?
Who are you?
Ripley. Ellen. Lieutenant First Class.
Number 36706.
Ellen Ripley died 200 years ago.
You're not her.
I'm not her?
- Who am I?
- You're a thing. a construct.
They grew you in a fucking lab.
And now they brought it out of you.
Not all the way out.
I can feel it.
Behind my eyes.
I can hear it moving.
Help me stop this thing before it gets loose.
It's too late.
You can't stop it.
It's inevitable.
Not as long as I'm around.
You'll never get out of here alive.
I don't care.
Really?
I can make it stop.
Go on. get out of here.
They're looking for you.
I think you're gonna find that this was
very ill-advised. Where are her friends?
- They're in the mess hall. sir.
- Well. you find them. now. Quietly!
- What the hell is goin' on here?
- Smells like a double-cross. boss.
Where's the other one? With the chair?
Don't ever touch me. Ever!
- Wanna tell us what this is?
- Wanna tell me who you're working for?
- Wren. they got nothing to do with this.
- To do with what?
Do you know the penalties
for terrorist activity?
No terrorists in my crew.
Call. got something to say?
I don't care whether you knew or not.
You brought a terrorist on board.
And as far as I am concerned.
you all die with her!
Do you understand?
Yeah.
I understand.
Christie.
Freeze!
Stop! Drop your weapons!
And you. drop that piece of shit!
Or I blow his head off!
- I can't do that. man.
- Drop it now!
- They're attached.
- I'm not fucking with you!
You're all under arrest
for a Code 8. concealed weapons.
and a Code 12. which is murder!
- Kiss my ass.
- Put down your weapons!
Everybody OK?
Real easy. soldier boy.
Security! There is a serious problem
in the mess hall.
You lie to me now. little girl.
I will cut your throat.
- We do not read you.
- Hello?
- We do not copy you. Please repeat.
Gediman.
He's conducting illegal experiments.
breeding...
- Ice the goddamn mole!
- Listen! He is breeding an alien species.
If it gets loose.
it'll make the Lacerta plague
- Look like a fucking square dance.
- Shut up!
Listen.
Your attention. please. Security breach.
Medlab. level 15.
Let's get back to the Betty.
The doctor and soldier boy can escort us.
What about Vriess?
Your attention. please.
Unauthorised opening of cage three.
Unauthorised opening of cages five.
seven. eight. ten.
- Move it!
- Evacuation.
- Go! Go! Go!
This is not a drill.
- Evacuation.
- Get on board!
Your attention. please.
Non-human presence detected.
Levels 21. 23.
27.
14.
Level 38.
Level 39.
Evacuation. Proceed to lifeboats.
This is not a drill.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'll give you holes. you slimy bastard!
Move it! Go!
- Final lifeboat ready for launch.
- Get aboard!
Go!
Complete evacuation now.
Grenade.
Evacuation incomplete.
Civilian presence detected in area H.
Warning: main vessel declared uninhabitable.
- Elgyn. come on. Let's move. man.
- Yeah.
Elgyn! Elgyn. where are you?
Elgyn!
Easy. Hillard!
- Give me a hand here!
- Get him up!
- Come on. let's get him up!
- Move out of the way!
Aw. shit.
- What the fuck did this?
- What's in this place?
- Call. get down!
- What the fuck is that?
Don't shoot!
It's in front of the hull!
- What is that?
- Come on. man. time to go.
Get back!
Time to go!
Come on. Call!
Open the goddamn door!
We can't open it! We can't open the door!
- We gotta go back!
- I'm not going back. You go back.
What the fuck...?
Was it everything you hoped for?
Leave him alone.
What do we do now. man?
Same thing we were doing.
We get the hell outta here.
What if there's more?
I say we stay here. man.
Let the army guys deal.
- Where the fuck are the army guys?
- They're dead.
- Then we don't need this asshole.
- Step back!
- You!
- Stop!
You got no authority here!
Doctor. that thing that killed my partner.
- That's your pet science project?
- Yes.
- Let me do him!
- I should let him do you right now.
How many more are there?
Twelve.
Twelve?
There'll be more.
So. who do I have to fuck
to get off this boat?
I can get you off. Maybe not the boat. but...
Let's go.
No. wait a second.
She was the host for these monsters.
Wren cloned her
because she had one inside her.
She's not human.
She was part of his experiment.
She will turn on us in a second.
- I don't give a shit what she is.
- She's too much of a risk.
- We have to leave her.
- She comes.
- We can't trust her.
- I don't trust anyone.
If we're gonna survive this mess.
we all stick together. Agreed?
Hillard. we gotta go.
It's not over. We gotta get to the Betty.
Make a nice souvenir.
- I can't believe you did that.
- Did what?
Killed one.
It's like killing your own kind.
It was in my way.
Oh. man!
Who were you expecting? Santa Claus?
I thought you were toast for certain. man.
Where's Elgyn?
- Shit.
- What if they're all over the Betty?
All the activity was in the F sector.
Why would they move?
They won't. If they send anyone out.
it'll be here.
Where the meat is.
Yeah... If we wanna make any decent time.
I say we ditch the cripple.
- No offence. man.
- None taken.
Nobody is left behind.
Not even you. Johner.
- What's the quickest way out?
- After the cooling tower. there's an elevator.
It runs from the top of the ship
down to level one.
- Straight to the dock.
- Sounds reasonable. Let's do it.
We're moving.
- What?
- The ship is moving. I can feel it.
The ship has stealth-run.
There's no way you can tell.
- She's right.
- The ship's been go since the attack.
It's a standard emergency procedure.
That's right. Any serious problem.
the ship autopilots to home base.
And you were planning on
letting us know this?
Nobody asked.
What's home base?
Earth.
- Great!
- Bastard!
Earth? I'd rather stay here
with the things. man.
- How long until we get to Earth?
- Three hours almost.
We gotta blow the ship.
Call! You're not blowing this ship.
Not while we're on it. OK?
You get out of the ship
you do as you please. all right?
Earth. man. What a shithole.
It's clear.
Hey. Ripley.
I heard you. like.
ran into these things before.
- That's right.
- Wow. man.
So. like. what did you do?
I died.
Not that way!
Ripley.
Ripley. come on.
Ripley. we got no time for sightseeing here.
Ripley. don't.
Kill...
me.
Kill me.
Don't do it. Ripley.
Don't do what?
What's the big deal. man?
Fuckin' waste of ammo.
Let's go.
Must be a chick thing.
Am I dreaming. or is this not
the shit we brought with us?
Yeah. It's the same shit.
It stinks in here. man. Let's keep moving.
Get away from me!
Get away!
- Drop the rod.
- Get away from me!
- Do it!
- Get away from me.
Get away from me.
Who are you people?
- What's happening here?
- Calm down.
What's happening here is that
we're getting the fuck off this ghost ship. OK?
Ship? What ship?
Where am I?
I was in cryo. right?
On my way to Xarem. right?
Work crew for the nickel refinery. right?
I wake up...
I know I don't understand.
Oh. God. I...
I saw... I saw horrible things.
Look. you're coming with us.
It's too dangerous for you here.
Leave him.
Fuck you! We're not leaving him here.
He's got one inside of him. I can smell it.
Inside me?
Inside me? What's inside me?
I don't want one of those things
birthing anywhere near my ass.
- It's a bad risk.
- What's inside me?
- We can'tjust leave him here.
- You came here to stop 'em spreading.
- What's inside me?
- Can't you stop it?
- We've got no time.
- We can't do it here.
I could do him. Back of the head.
- What's inside me?
- There's got to be another way.
- What if we freeze him?
- What's in-fucking-side me?
A parasite!
A foreign element.
There's a monster in your chest.
These guys hijacked your ship.
and they sold your cryotube to this human.
And he put an alien inside of you.
It's a really nasty one.
And in a few hours. it will burst its way
through your ribcage.
and you're gonna die.
Any questions?
Who are you?
I'm the monster's mother.
If we freeze him on the Betty.
the doctor can remove it later.
- Fine by me.
- Since when were you in goddamn charge?
Since you were born without balls!
Ease off. people!
All right. you come with us.
You might even live.
Get twitchy on me. you'll be shot.
Let's move out.
It's a mess down there. Is this the only way?
Vriess! We gotta lose the chair.
I know.
- Kawlang maneuver. right?
- Yeah. Just like old times.
Yeah.
Must be the cooling tanks.
Somebody must have opened the valves.
The nasties couldn't do that. could they?
We're at the bottom of the ship.
We have to go through the kitchen.
Maybe 90ft.
To the elevator on the other side.
- I don't like it.
- What's to like?
- This sucks!
- Wren. are you sure about the distance?
Yes!
- You ready to get wet. partner?
- Yeah.
Hey. will your weapons fly underwater?
They're disposables. They can take it.
Disposables?
Hey. I heard about those.
- How many rounds?
- 20.
Split points give you a good hole.
even if it's smaller caliber.
That's cool!
They're big with hitters
'cause you throw 'em away after the job.
I wouldn't like to throw away a weapon
I'm attached to.
Yeah.
Guess I don't have to tell everyone
to take a deep breath.
When we hit the surface. no backstroke. OK?
Jesus Christ!
They set a goddamn trap.
It's a goddamn ambush!
Distephano!
It won't break.
Give me your weapon.
You really are way too trusting.
No!
You killed her! You bastard!
I'll get you!
Father. lock the door!
Christie! Climb!
Climb! Come on!
Come on!
It's jammed! Move it!
It's jammed!
Get off my foot. bitch!
Johner!
Get off me!
Die. motherfucker!
Do it. man!
Real nice party. ain't it?
Christie!
No!
What are you doing? Don't do it!
Don't!
We can make it!
No!
Damn!
This way.
Come on!
Baby. am I glad to see you!
I was sure that asshole got you. Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
- You got body armour on?
- Yeah. Come on.
You took it in the chest. I saw it.
You're a robot?
Son of a bitch! Our little Call
is just full of surprises.
I should've known.
No human being is that humane.
I thought synthetics were logical.
You just a big old psycho. girl!
- You're a robot?
- You're a Second Gen. aren't you?
You're an Auton.
Robots designed by robots. right?
- Ha!
- That's right. I remember.
They were meant to revitalise
the synthetic industry.
Instead they buried it.
They don't like being told what to do.
The government ordered a recall.
Now. I heard...
I heard that only a few
had gotten out in time.
Man. I never thought that I would see one!
Great. She's a toaster oven.
Can we leave now?
- How long before we land?
- Two hours.
Vriess. you got a wrench?
Maybe she just needs an oil change.
Sorry. Access denied.
- And I almost fucked it.
- Like you never fucked a robot!
If Wren gets in the computer.
he could screw us.
- We gotta find a terminal.
- There's no console on this level.
- We'd have to go back.
- We can't go back.
- And I don't know Wren's access codes.
- Help me.
Call...
No. I can't.
Right. You're the new model droid.
You can access the mainframe by remote.
No. I can't.
I burned my modem. We all did.
Call. you can still patch in manually.
You know that.
There's ports in the chapel. up there.
Call...
- You're programmed for that?
- Don't make me do this.
Don't make me make you.
I don't wanna go in there.
It's like my insides are liquid. It's not real.
Get over it. You can blow this ship.
before it reaches Earth.
and kill them all.
Just give us time to get out first.
- Damn it!
- Anything?
Hold on.
Breach in sector seven. sector three.
Sector nine unstable.
Engines operating at 41%.
86 minutes until Earth dock.
We burned too much energy.
I can't make critical mass. I can't blow it.
Then crash it.
I'm OK. I'm OK.
I feel good.
Ground level recalibrated.
New destination: 7-6-0-4-0-3.
Uninhabited quadrant.
Braking system's offline.
Deceleration increase.
Time until impact
now 43 minutes. 8 seconds.
Try to clear us a path to the Betty.
And start her up.
Please wait.
Emergency override
in console 45V. level one.
It's Wren. He's almost at the Betty.
Father. locate the power drain. Report.
Father?
Father's dead. asshole.
Intruder on level one.
All aliens. please proceed to level one.
You got a mean streak.
Damn it!
- Let me see.
- Don't touch me.
Come on.
You must think this is pretty funny.
I'm finding a lot of things funny lately.
But I don't think they are.
Why do you go on living?
How can you stand being what you are?
Not much choice.
At least there's a part of you that's human.
I'm just...
Look at me.
I'm disgusting.
Why did you come here?
To kill you. Remember?
Before the recall.
I accessed the mainframe.
Every dirty little covert op
the government ever dreamed up is in there.
And this. you. the aliens.
even the crew from the Betty.
I knew if they succeeded
it'd be the end of them.
- Why do you care?
- I'm programmed to.
You're programmed to be an asshole?
You're the new asshole model
they're putting out?
Come on.
I couldn't watch 'em do it.
I couldn't let 'em annihilate themselves.
Do you understand that?
I did once.
I tried to save people.
It didn't work out.
There was this girl.
She had bad dreams.
I tried to help her.
She died.
Now I can't even remember her name.
I guess we're almost there.
Right.
- Do you dream?
- I... We have neural processors. Yes.
When I sleep I dream about them. It.
Every night.
All around me. In me.
I used to be afraid to dream.
but I'm not anymore.
Why?
Because. no matter how bad the dreams get.
when I wake up it's always worse.
- It's not so far now!
- God. I'm so tired!
Oh. no. This is bad. right?
I think we're near the nest.
- We'll go another way.
- We don't have time.
- We got 90 minutes.
- Not any more.
What?
- What did you do. robot?
- Let's go. Come on.
Hey! You wanna die here with
your brothers and sisters. that's cool.
But I plan to live past today.
If this hunk of plastic is pullin' any shit.
I'm gonna kill her!
Kill you!
Does that compute?
Or do I have to draw you a schematic?
Hey!
You want another souvenir?
- How far are the docks?
- 100 yards.
Ripley?
Come on!
Ripley. we have to go.
I hear them. I hear them. They're so close.
- Ripley...
- It's the queen.
She's in pain.
Ripley!
Wait!
Oh. my God.
We gotta be moving. The best thing
we can do is pray for a quick death.
Come on. Come on.
- It's not right.
- I've been saying that all day.
Call. I need you to patch into
the ship again. and open the hatch.
Johner. we should put Purvis
in the freezer now.
All right. little buddy.
Nap time.
Nobody moves. or I put a cap
right where this little droid's brain is.
- Distephano. take the weapons.
- Begging your pardon. sir. but fuck you!
Fine. Then I kill her.
and you kill me. and we all die.
and nobody goes home!
Now drop the weapon!
Then this little synthetic bitch
is gonna plug into the Auriga
and she is gonna take us back to home base.
according to standard emergency procedures.
- No. she's not!
- Are you crazy?
You still wanna bring those things
back to Earth?
- Haven't you been paying attention?
- The intellectual speaks!
- Listen. if...
- Don't you ever shut up?
Why does nobody listen to me?
I told you. at first everything was normal.
The queen laid her eggs.
But then she started to change.
She added a second cycle. so...
So...
this time there is no host.
There are no eggs.
There is only her womb
and the creature inside.
That is Ripley's gift to her:
a human reproductive system.
She is giving birth for you. Ripley.
And now she is perfect!
You are...
a beautiful butterfly.
No!
No! No...
Look.
Your beautiful. beautiful little baby.
Look. it thinks you're its mother.
Come on.
Civilian vessel online.
Emergency departure authorised.
All right. she's hot. I'll open the Auriga's
air locks. Pull the holding clamps.
Right. I just need to find
the vertical thrust lock.
- Are you sure you can fly this thing?
- Yes!
Launch status is go.
No!
Ripley!
- Hey.
- I thought you were dead.
I get that a lot.
- Why are we still here?
- I'm just finding the manual override.
- For Christ's sake!
- Hey. Ripley.
Good memory. Excuse me.
- Ripley's back.
- Is that it?
Nope.
You can't fly one of these things?
Are you kidding?
This piece of shit is older than I am.
Goddammit! We still got breach. The hatch.
- I closed it.
- I've fixed it a hundred times!
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Approaching Earth's atmosphere.
Window of departure now 46 seconds.
Call? We have to go.
Call.
We've gotta get out of here.
Window of departure now 20 seconds.
Grab on to something. Call. We're outta here.
Come on. baby.
This thing is gonna fall apart!
Pressure's unstable!
Go help Call turn on the auxiliary pump!
Distephano?
Come on! Step on it!
Hey! I'm not the mechanic here. Ironside!
I mostly just hurt people!
Shit!
Call!
Call. get back up here!
Call! Call!
Ripley!
Hey. Ripley!
Johner. where are you. you son of a bitch?
Get on it. bastard!
- What am I supposed to do?
- Grab the sticks!
Put her down.
Ripley!
I'm sorry.
USM Auriga will impact in five seconds. Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Thank you.
- What's burning?
- Us!
Shit! You're right!
So this is Earth. huh?
This is Earth.
It's my first time here.
I suppose the military'll be
sniffing around here pretty soon.
Bet you're not too anxious to see them.
Not really.
You know. a person could get pretty lost
around here if they wanted to.
What do you think?
What shall we do?
I don't know.
I'm a stranger here myself.
Visiontext Subtitles: Stephanie Donohue
US ENGLISH